Guide to the Nasri Fuleihan Collection AD.MC.056
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Nasri Fuleihan Collection
  - A man and two boys at the House of Simon the Tanner, Jaffa., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref173; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Boys; Men; Hats; Jaffa; Regional/National Dress; Outdoors; English Writing; Palestine; Group Portraits; Turbans
  - Men with horses and camels in front of tents., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref174; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Camels; Horses; Animals; Regional/National Dress; Guns; Tents; Donkeys; Outdoors; Palestine; Group Portraits; Turbans
  - Group portrait of men with Nasri Fuleihan (third from the left)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref175; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 13.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Fez/Tarboush; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Outdoors; Palestine; Buildings; Turbans
  - Group portrait of men and a woman, including Nasri Fuleihan (on the far left) on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref176; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Smoking; Hats; Bow Ties; Jerusalem; Palestine; Tobacco pipes; Hotels; Outdoors
  - Portrait of a man standing in front of a tree, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref177; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Smoking; Hats; Palm Trees; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Palestine; Tobacco pipes
  - A boy leading two women riding donkeys (linked ref216)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref178; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Women; Children; Boys; Donkeys; Animals; Hats; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - A man leaning on a railing by a dam., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref179; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 9.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Dams/Barrages; Hats; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; North America; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
  - Two men standing on a rock formation., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref180; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 X 9.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Hats; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Bags/Purses; Unknown Locations; Group Portraits
  - A clergyman inside the Tomb of the Virgin Mary, Jerusalem., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref181; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.4 X 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Church of the Sepulchre of Saint Mary/Tomb of Saint Mary; Religious Crosses; Religious Sites; Religious Imagery; Priests/Clergymen; Books; Lanterns/Lamps; Jerusalem; Furnishings; English Writing; Palestine; Individual Portraits
  - Tomb of Isaac and Rebecca in the Tombs of the Patriarchs, Hebron, West Bank., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref182; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.9 X 9.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Sanctuary of Abraham/Ibrahimi Mosque; Mosques; Religious Sites; Tombs/Mausoleums; Lanterns/Lamps; Palestine
  - Sarah's Tomb in the Tombs of the Patriarchs, Hebron., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref183; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.2 X 8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Carpets/Rugs; English Writing; Arabic Writing; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Doors/Entrances; Palestine; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Tomb of Leah in the Tombs of the Patriarchs, Hebron., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref184; Raad, Khalil (Chalil), 1854-1957; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.6 X 9.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Embroidery; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; English Writing; Palestine; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Entrance to Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Dead Sea with Libdawi (?), boatman, in foreground, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref185; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.1 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mountains/Hills; Rivers; Guns; Regional/National Dress; Dead Sea; Ma'in, Jordan; Men; Outdoors; Individual Portraits
  - Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref186; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Ma'in, Jordan; Mountains/Hills; Palm Trees; English Writing; Outdoors; Landscapes
  - Portrait of a man on a horse., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref187; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Men; Regional/National Dress; Animals; Tents; Outdoors; Palestine; Individual Portraits
  - Two men ride camels while holding guns., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref188; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Guns; Canes/Walking Sticks; Camels; Animals; Outdoors; Palestine; Weapons; Group Portraits
  - Men standing on top of stone building (linked ref172)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref189; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 13.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Buildings; Regional/National Dress; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Turbans
  - Village of Al-Eizariya (Bethany)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref190; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Al-Eizariya/Bethany; Buildings; Landscapes; Palestine
  - Person entering the Church of Nativity. (same as ref95), Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref191; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Church of the Nativity; Jerusalem; Men; Buildings; Palestine
  - Church of Saint Anne (Khirbet Sandahanna), Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref192; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin); Palestine; Religious Sites; English Writing; Landscapes
  - Church of Saint Anne (Khirbet Sandahanna), Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref193; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.7cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Religious Sites; Bayt Jibrin (Beit Guvrin); Palestine; English Writing
  - Ibrahimi Mosque/Cave of Patriarchs, Hebron., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref194; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hebron/Al-Khalil; Cave of the Patriarchs/Cave of Machpelah/Al-Haram al-Ibrahimi; Mosques; Tombs/Mausoleums; Religious Sites; Palestine; Men; Camels; Horses; Animals
  - Cliffs South of Wadi Kelb, Dead Sea, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref195; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; Jordan; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; English Writing
  - Acacia tree at Ein Gedi, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref196; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.9 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Ain Jidi/Ein Gedi; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Landscapes; Agriculture/Farms; English Writing; Palestine
  - Badland formations below Masada, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref197; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.7 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Masada; Palestine; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; English Writing
  - Group portrait of men and a woman outdoors (right hand side) (linked ref200)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref198; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Outdoors; Furnishings
  - Launch and camp at Hammam in Wadi Zarqa Ma'in., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref199; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Ma'in, Jordan; Jordan; Boats/Ships; Water; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes
  - Group portrait of men and a woman outdoors (linked ref198)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref200; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Outdoors; Drinks/Beverages; Hats
  - A group portrait of men in front of tents (linked ref77)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref201; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Tents; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Guns; Weapons; Boys; Children; Turbans
  - Man standing with a gun (linked ref208)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref202; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Smoking; Cigarettes; Guns; Weapons; Hats; Outdoors; Nude/Naked
  - A man standing in front of the Minbar Burhan al-Din (Minbar al-Sayf)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref203; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 X 8.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Al-Aqsa Mosque/al-Masjid al-ʾAqṣā; Mosques; Religious Sites; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Men; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Palestine; Jerusalem
  - A man and woman on horses., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref204; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 7.8 X 10.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Horses; Animals; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Hats
  - A group portrait of women, men and children in front of a tent (linked to ref267)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref205; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 X 14.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Boys; Children; Donkeys; Animals; Group Portraits; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Bow Ties; Tents; Facial Hair
  - Augusta Victoria Hospital., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref206; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Jerusalem; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Palestine; Hospitals; Churches; Agriculture/Farms; Landscapes
  - Salt pillar 100 ft high, west of Jebel Usdum (Mount Sodom)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref207; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Mount Sodom/Jebel Usdum, Newe Zohar; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Palestine
  - A man crouching next to a dog and a dead bird (linked ref202)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref208; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 11 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Dogs; Animals; Hats; Group Portraits
  - Wadi Mujib., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref209; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14.3cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; Jordan; Rivers; Mountains/Hills; Water; Landscapes
  - Marlstone (marl) rock formation of a cave 2 miles S.E. of Iraq Al-Manshiyya., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref210; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Caves; English Writing
  - Three men, two of which hold cameras., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref211; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 12.5 X 9.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Group Portraits; Cameras; Hats
  - A man standing besides machinery., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref212; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.1 X 10.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown Locations; Men; Machines; Factories; Civil Engineering; Workers; Individual Portraits
  - Two men standing in front of tent, one holds a cooking pan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref213; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Tents; Food; Tea/Coffee; Deserts
  - A mountainous landscape in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref214; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Jordan
  - View of the Dome of the Rock and Jerusalem from the Mount of Olives., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref215; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Buildings; Agriculture/Farms; Religious Sites; Palestine; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Landscapes
  - A boy leading three women on donkeys (linked ref178)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref216; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Women; Boys; Children; Donkeys; Animals; Group Portraits; Hats; Buildings
  - The 'Tree of the Agony' in the Garden of Gethsemane., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref218; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.3 X 8.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Gethsemane, Jerusalem; Gardens; Religious Sites; Palestine
  - A man sitting on rock in front of a wadi in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref219; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Jordan
  - Men with camels and horses., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref220; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Horses; Camels; Animals; Group Portraits; Weapons; Guns; Regional/National Dress; Tents; Outdoors; Donkeys
  - Six men riding horses and camels in front of a mountain range., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref221; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.9 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Horses; Animals; Weapons; Guns; Mountains/Hills; Camels; Group Portraits
  - Eight men riding camels and horses., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref222; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Horses; Animals; Tents; Flags; Weapons; Guns; Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress; Camels
  - The rooftops of the Church of the Holy Sepulchre, the Mosque of Omar and the Lutheran Church of the Redeemer., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref223; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.2 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Church of the Holy Sepulchre; Jerusalem; English Writing; Religious Sites; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Buildings; Mosques; Churches; Mountains/Hills; Religious Crosses; Palestine; Landscapes
  - Portrait of a man sitting at a café (linked ref243, 244)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref224; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 6.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Restaurants/bars; Tiles; Hats
  - People posing by a car., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref225; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.4 X 13.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Cars/Trucks; Transportation; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Bow Ties; Cigarettes; Smoking; Group Portraits; Buildings
  - Masada Fortress., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref226; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 15.2 X 8.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Masada; English Writing; Forts/Castles; Landscapes; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palestine
  - Masada Fortress., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref227; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Masada; Forts/Castles; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; English Writing; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - North side of entrance to Wadi Zarqa Ma'in, Dead Sea, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref228; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 X 14.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; English Writing; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Ma'in, Jordan; Jordan
  - Landscape of Kornub village (Qarnab Abu Silb) with handwritten notes relating to geographical features and well drilling., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref229; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 14.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Qarnab Abu Silb (Kornub); Petroleum industry and trade.; English Writing; Landscapes; Mountains/Hills; Palestine
  - A man holding dead birds., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref230; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 X 8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Palestine; Men; Animals; Individual Portraits
  - A man on horse holding a cane., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref231; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 X 8.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Individual Portraits; Horses; Regional/National Dress; Agriculture/Farms
  - Men and horses in a field., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref232; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 5.7 X 8.1 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Horses; Animals; Men; Palestine; Group Portraits
  - Plains and shrub land., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref233; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes
  - Group portrait of men, including Ismail Bey el Husseini (linked ref248)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref234; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 14.5 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Umbrellas/Parasols; Smoking; Cigarettes; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Tents; Flags; Bow Ties; Civil Engineering
  - Men and women posing in a wadi in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref235; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 11.3 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Water; Rivers; Mountains/Hills; Jordan
  - Group portrait of men and women on the roof of Amdursky's Hotel., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref236; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 X 14 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Hotels; Jaffa Gate, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Men; Women; Buildings; Fez/Tarboush; Bow Ties; Hats; Smoking; Cigarettes; Canes/Walking Sticks; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Jewelry; Palestine; Hotels; Group Portraits
  - Ruins of a stone wall., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref237; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 14.6 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
  - Waterfall in Wadi Kelb, Dead Sea., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref238; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.7 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dead Sea; Waterfalls; Mountains/Hills; Palestine; Landscapes; Water
  - Jewish cemetery on the slopes of the Mount of Olives, Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref239; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.2 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Mount of Olives/Jabal al-Zaytun, Jerusalem; Jerusalem; Cemeteries; Religious Sites; Men; Palestine; Landscapes
  - People walking on a downhill near a building in Palestine or Jordan., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref240; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 X 11.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Buildings; Women; Men; Canes/Walking Sticks; Bags/Purses; Mountains/Hills; Agriculture/Farms; Palm Trees; Jordan; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref241; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.3 X 8.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Dome of the Rock/Qubbat al-Sakhrah; Temple Mount/al-Ḥaram al-Šarīf; Jerusalem; Palestine; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Mosques
  - A aerial view of buildings and a church., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref242; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 X 8.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Landscapes; Buildings; Agriculture/Farms
  - Group portrait of four men at a café (linked ref224, 244)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref243; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 6.2 X 8.8 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Group Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Furnishings; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Restaurants/bars; Tiles; Hats
  - Portrait of a man sitting at a café (linked ref224,243)., Circa 1910s - 1930s; ref244; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 X 6.2 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Palestine; Men; Fez/Tarboush; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Tiles; Restaurants/bars; Hats
  - Abdülhamid II clock tower, Jaffa Gate., Circa 1908 - 1922; ref245; Fuleihan, Nasri Suleiman; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 X 8.4 cm (Object 056 Digital Copy Only)